NILOUFAR KHAEFI

Full-stack developer

I am primarily a frontend developer with some experience in backend development. I have worked extensively with JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Angular, and Node.js. My focus is on creating user-friendly, modern web applications using React and Angular.

During my internship at Atomic Learning, I worked on a React-based MERN stack project. Currently, I am part of an incredible internship where I am focusing on frontend development, working with Angular, TypeScript, and Figma, while also gaining experience with gRPC and understanding workflows in a larger company.

Additionally, I am joining the QA Bootcamp at Hack Your Future to deepen my understanding of software quality assurance and testing methodologies. I would also like to expand my skills and knowledge by contributing to new projects.



- +45 61 76 55 96
- nilooooofar97@gmail.com
- Rissko, Næringen
- Linkedin | Github

EDUCATION

Full-stack Web Development bootcamp

Hack your future Sep.2023 - Jul.2024

React course

ReDi School Sep.2023 - Dec.2023

Javascript course

ReDi School Mar.2023 - Jun.2023

Bachelor of Textile Engineering

Isfahan University of Technology, Iran 2017- 2021

SKILLS

HTML CSS

TailwindCSS

Javascript

Typescript

React

Node.js

Angular

.Net

MySQL

MongoDB

Git

Scrum

figma

EXPERIENCE

Risskov Teknik og Solar

FrontEnd developer, Internship

Nov 2024 - current

As a Frontend Developer, I work on designing and maintaining the admin page using Angular and Angular Material. I also use gRPC for smooth and efficient data communication, focusing on creating a user-friendly and scalable interface.

Hack Your Future

Mentor and Teaching Assistant

Oct 2024 - current

As a mentor, I will teach HTML and CSS to new students and support other sessions as a teaching assistant.

Atomic Learning Systems

Full-stack developer, internship

Mar 2024 - Aug 2024

Frontend Developer focused on building user-facing components with expertise in React, Redux Toolkit, RTK Query, Tailwind CSS, Restful api, MongoDB, and Node.js.

DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

Portfolio

A portfolio website designed by HTML, CSS, and Javascript which includes my personal skills and experiences

Memory Game

A memory game designed by HTML, CSS, and Javascript where players can test their memory skilled in 2 levels.

Meal Sharing

It's a website developed in React and node.js where people can sell their homemade meal or reserve their favourite food.

Atomic Learning Landingspage

This is the final project of the Hack Your Future course, developed by our team of six using the Scrum methodology. We utilized technologies such as React, TailwindCSS, and Git to complete the project.

LANGUAGE

- English fluent
- Danish intermediate
- Farsi native